bagas : Today we will vote on the design of our group, namely Muhammad Bagas Pradana, Adi Rahman, Moh. Falend Wandamen
Bagas : thank you to yusrizal piliyang and brother mushab utsmani who have been willing to be reviewers of our design
Bagas : I immediately started, I got permission to do a share screen
Bagas : is already visible?
Utsman : yes, already seen
Bagas : i mmediately explained
Bagas : well, it looks like there are several designs. there is a design of the application, alternative design 1 and alternative design 2
Bagas : Well Adi can tell you what application we want to review
Adi : This application is an AR application where when we point the camera at the poster, the information will appear, inreality
Bagas : good, thanks for the explanation brother Adi. now let's go to the review agenda session of the design itself
Bagas : the first review, do you want from yusrizal, or utsman? it could also be from myself, the first review
utsman : hmm, just from bagas firstly
bagas : well, the first one we can see that