Adi : In here..
Adi : we use the InReality application.
Bagas : Yes.
Adi : This application is made like a learning medium for getting to know certain planets
Adi : by using a poster and then the use of AR technology so it seems like the planet appears.
Adi : there are three application menu.
Adi : the first is AR Camera, the second is the HINT, and the third is the poster
Adi : In my opinion, from the start there is no button to turn off the music.
Bagas : yes, there was no button to turn off the music
Falend : suddenly straight away
Adi : so maybe later you will add a button symbol to turn off the music
Bagas : yes it can be added
Adi : do you think the menu itself is proportional?
Bagas : it could have been made even better
Falend : the menu itself in the hint section, it shouldn't need to be combined into the main part, in my opinion
Falend : Yes, the hint means it's like being positioned like the help button in the corner
Adi  : So the main feature is the AR Camera, put it in the middle screen